http://www.dispenser.com/pages/privacy-policy

0
Your cart is currently empty.
Home
/
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
We Respect Your Privacy!
We recognize your right to confidentiality and pledge to protect your privacy. We only collect personally identifying information (name, e-mail address, address and telephone number) about persons interacting with us when knowingly provided by them. Personally identifiable information will not be sold or otherwise transferred to third parties.
Acceptance
By providing such information, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.
Information We Collect and How We Use It
The personally identifiable information we may collect would consist of first and last name, street address, city, province/state, postal code, country, telephone number, e-mail address and subject of inquiry. In the case of a purchase, we also collect:
Method of payment, items ordered and amount of the purchase.
We process standard credit card information (card number, card type and expiration date). Processing, when done electronically, is done via a secure, encrypted session.
Where necessary, we also collect information required for shipping.
Safe Keeping of Information
We maintain records of all purchases.
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure correct use of information, we maintain physical, electronic and administrative safeguards to secure the information we collect. All information is accessible only by authorized staff. We may disclose personal information to a successor organization provided that entity abides by this or a similar privacy policy.
We May Change Our Privacy Policy
Better Living Products reserves the right to change our privacy policy. Our privacy policy will be kept up to date. To view our privacy policy, please visit www.betterlivingproductsusa.com
Search our store
